Guide to the Judson Memorial Church Archive MSS.094
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series G: Media
  - Subseries 1: Audiocassettes
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - "All Things Considered" show on Hookers, 1980, ID: 094.0119 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0119, Case 094.0119)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      CD access copy available by appointment.
    - "All Things Considered" 6/10/1986, Women's Day Survey, Spa Lady Commentary by Carmen Delzell, ID: 094.0120 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0120, Case 094.0120)
    - Archive Committee Meeting, 3/3/1977, ID: 094.0121 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0121, Case 094.0121_pt.1, Case 094.0121_pt.2)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Please request part 1 and part 2.
    - Baptist Hymns and Familiar Sacred Songs, undated; ID: 094.0122 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0122, Case 094.0122_pt.1, Case 094.0122_pt.2)
    - Building Committee Meeting, 11/9/19--?, undated; ID: 094.0123 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0123, Case 094.0123)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Part 1 and part 2 on same disc.
    - Building Council, 11/9/19--?, undated; ID: 094.0124 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0124, Case 094.0124)
    - Christmas in Concert, 12/14/1986, ID: 094.0125 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0125, Case 094.0125)
    - Churchman at Attica, 12/13/1971, ID: 094.0126 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0126, Case 094.0126)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Please request part 1 and part 2..
    - Dickason, undated; ID: 094.0127 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0127, Case 094.0127)
    - "Double Steal" by Jeremy Wall/"Grand Prix" by Ronnie Foster, undated; ID: 094.0128 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0128, Case 094.0128)
    - Fundamentalism-Scott Appleby, 4/8/1990, ID: 094.0129 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0129, Case 094.0129)
    - Henderson, Joseph, American Indian and Jungian Orientation, undated; ID: 094.0130 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0130, Case 094.0130_pt.1, Case 094.0130_pt.2)
    - Housing Works with Arlene Carmen, undated; ID: 094.0131 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0131, Case 094.0131)
    - Judson Worship Service, 2/26/1989, ID: 094.0132 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0132, Case 094.0132)
    - Kerygma II, conversation with Al Carmines and other material, 4/1978, ID: 094.0133A (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0133A, Case 094.0133A)
    - The King's Singers Christmas Songs, 1980, ID: 094.0134 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0134)
      Currently unavailable.
    - Life Resource Center Mediation, 1978, ID: 094.0135 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0135, Case 094.0135_pt.1, Case 094.0135_pt.2)
    - Lind-Snyder, Steve. "Worship Life, Not Death." (for Moody's 25th anniversary), undated; ID: 094.0136 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0136, Case 094.0136)
    - McNutt, Ken. Interview with Moody regarding Judson House, 1/1998, ID: 094.0137 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0137, Case 094.0137)
    - Moody in Harlem, 2/27/1983, ID: 094.0138 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0138, Case 094.0138)
    - O'Driscoll, Dean Herbert. "Changing Ministry.", undated; ID: 094.0139 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0139, Case 094.0139)
    - Oyl, Irving. 9/1978, ID: 094.0140 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0140, Case 094.0140_pt.1, Case 094.0140_pt.2)
    - "Peace" by Al Carmines, undated; ID: 094.0141 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0141)
    - Remembrances of the Years of Robert Spike's Ministry, undated; ID: 094.0142 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0142, Case 094.0142_pt.1, Case 094.0142_pt.2)
    - Sander, Donald. "Symbolic Shamanism", undated; ID: 094.0143 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0143, Case 094.0143)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1970's, 1970-1979; ID: 094.0144 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0144, Case 094.0144_pt.1, Case 094.0144_pt.2)
    - "Somebody's Calling My Name." Canaan Baptist Church of Christ, 1979, ID: 094.0145 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0145)
    - Unidentified, Numbered Cassettes (1, 2, 3), undated; ID: 094.0146 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0146, Media ID: 094.0147, Media ID: 094.0148, Case 094.0146, Case 094.0147, Case 094.0148)
    - Unidentified Worship Service, undated; cuid7056 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0149, Case 094.0149_pt.1, Case 094.0149_pt.2)
    - Unknown Male/Choral Music/Carmines singing "Life Is Just a Sometime Thing", undated; ID: 094.0150 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0150, Case 094.0150)
    - Washington March, undated; ID: 094.0151 (Box 75, Media ID: 094.0151, Case 094.0151_pt.1, Case 094.0151_pt.2)
    - "Welfare Hostage" with Howard Moody and Steve Lind-Snyder, undated; ID: 094.0152 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0152)
      CD access copy is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only.
  - Subseries 2: Audio Reels
    - Reels-"About Time" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0153 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0153, Case 094.0153_pt.1, Case 094.0153_pt.2)
    - Reels-75th Anniversary Celebration, undated; ID: 094.0154 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0154, Case 094.0154)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Parts 1, 2 and 3 on one disc.
    - Reels-75th Anniversary Service, undated; ID: 094.0155 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0155, Case 094.0155)
    - Reels-Carmines at Judson Memorial Church, undated; ID: 094.0156 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0156, Case 094.0156)
    - Reels-"Christmas Rappings" at Judson Memorial Church, undated; ID: 094.0158 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0158, Case 094.0158)
    - Reels-"Discotheque a Go-Go" Various Artists, undated; ID: 094.0159 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0159)
    - Reels-Destruction Concert with Ralph Ortiz (Piano and Chicken)1967, ID: 094.0080 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0080, Case 094.0080)
    - Reels-"Flares" by Philip Corner, undated; ID: 094.0086 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0086, Case 094.0086, Box Digitized Access Files, File 094.0086_s)
    - Reels-"Lucinda's Pastime" by Philip Corner, undated; ID: 094.0087 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0087, Case 094.0087)
    - Reels-"The Faggot" Judson Poet's Theater, Side One, undated; ID: 094.0160 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0160, Case 094.0160)
    - Reels-"The Faggot" Judson Poet's Theater, Side Two, undated; ID: 094.0161 (Box 76, Media ID: 094.0161, Case 094.0161)
    - Reels-Folk Songs, undated; ID: 094.0162 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0162, Case 094.0162)
    - Reels-"Future" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0163 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0163, Case 094.0163_pt.1, Case 094.0163_pt.2)
    - Reels-Home Movies I, undated; ID: 094.0164 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0164, Case 094.0164)
    - Reels-Home Movie II, undated; ID: 094.0165 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0165, Case 094.0165)
    - Reels-"Joan" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0166 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0166, Case 094.0166_pt.1, Case 094.0166_pt.2)
    - Reels-"Life of a Man" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0167 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0167, Case 094.0167_pt.1, Case 094.0167_pt.2)
    - Reels-"Listen to Me" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0168 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0168, Case 094.0168_pt.1, Case 094.0168_pt.2)
    - Reels-"A Look at the 50's" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0169 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0169, Case 094.0169)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Part 1 and part on one disc.
    - Reels-"The Making of Americans" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0170 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0170, Case 094.0170_pt.1a, Case 094.0170_pt.1b, Case 094.0170_pt.2)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Please request part 1a and 1b and part 2.
    - Reels-Morning Worship/Brent and Art/John Windgate, undated; ID: 094.0171 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0171, Case 094.0171)
    - Reels-Neville, Phoebe, undated; ID: 094.0172 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0172, Case 094.0172)
      CD access copy available by appointment. Part 1 and part 2 on one disc.
    - Reels-Poems and Satire by Ed Blair, Stan Fischer, S. Bernard, undated; ID: 094.0173 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0173, Case 094.0173_pt.1a, Case 094.0173_pt.1b, Case 094.0173_pt.2)
    - Reels-"Pomegranda" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0174 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0174, Case 094.0174)
    - Reels-"Religion" Judson Poets' Theater, 11/1973, ID: 094.0175 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0175)
    - Reels-"Religion" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0176 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0176)
    - Reels-"Religion" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0177 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0177)
    - Reels-"Religion" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0178 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0178)
    - Reels-Remembering, undated; ID: 094.0179 (Box 77, Media ID: 094.0179)
    - Reels-"San Francisco's Burning" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0180 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0180)
    - Reels-"San Francisco's Burning" Judson Poets' Theater-Act I, undated; ID: 094.0181 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0181)
    - Reels-"San Francisco's Burning" Judson Poets' Theater-Act II, part 1, undated; ID: 094.0182 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0182)
    - Reels-"San Francisco's Burning" Judson Poets' Theater-Act II, part 2, undated; ID: 094.0183 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0183)
    - Reels-"Snow White" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0184 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0184)
    - Reels-"Song of Songs" Judson Poets' Theater-Part 1, undated; ID: 094.0185 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0185)
    - Reels-"Song of Songs" Judson Poets' Theater-Part 2, undated; ID: 094.0186 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0186)
    - Reels-Sound Effects, Beatles Songs, Information on Nazi Leaders, etc., undated; ID: 094.0187 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0187)
    - Reels-Tennessee Waltz/Rain, undated; ID: 094.0189 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0189)
    - Reels-That's Life/Blue Eyes/O Princess Daughter-Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0190 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0190)
    - Reels-Toche Statement, undated; ID: 094.0085 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0085)
    - Reels-Unidentified Discussion or Worship, undated; ID: 094.0191 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0191)
    - Reels-Unidentified (original artwork on case), undated; ID: 094.0192 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0192)
    - Reels-Unidentified, undated; ID: 094.0193 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0193)
    - Reels-"Urban Crisis" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0194A (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0194A)
    - Reels-"Urban Crisis" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0195 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0195)
    - Reels-"Wanted" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0196 (Box 78, Media ID: 094.0196)
    - Reels-Selections from "W. C." Judson Poets' Theater-Part 1, undated; ID: 094.0197 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0197)
    - Reels-Selections from "W. C." Judson Poets' Theater-Part 2, undated; ID: 094.0198 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0198)
    - Reels-The Weavers at Carnegie Hall, v. 2, undated; ID: 094.0199 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0199)
    - Reels-"West Side Story" Oscar Peterson Trio, undated; ID: 094.0200 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0200)
    - Reels-"Where Has the City Gone?" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0201 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0201)
    - Reels-"Winnie the Pooh" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0202 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0202)
    - Reels-"Wrong Side Out" Judson Poets' Theater, undated; ID: 094.0203 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0203)
    - Reels-Various Commercial Rock, undated; ID: 094.0204 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0204)
    - Reels-Various Musical Recordings, undated; ID: 094.0205 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0205)
    - Reels-Various Radio Programs, News, etc., undated; ID: 094.0206 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0206)
    - Reels-Various Rock and Jazz, undated; ID: 094.0207 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0207)
    - Reels-Various Symphonies, Rock, and Opera, undated; ID: 094.0208 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0208)
    - Reels-Violin Piece, undated; ID: 094.0209 (Box 79, Media ID: 094.0209)
  - Subseries 3: Videorecordings
    - ACLU "A Conference in Defense of Roe vs. Wade" 10/5/1989., ID: 094.0001 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0001, Case 094.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Original Format: VHS videocassette
      Duration: 00:36:00
      DVD access copy available.
    - Christmas Rappings (Carmines) Parts I and II., 1989; ID: 094.0002 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0002, Case 094.0002)
      Duration: 01:32:00
    - H.W. [Unidentified woman speaking about false arrest]., undated; ID: 094.0003 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0003, Box Shared Fales PM 13, Case 094.0030, Case 094.0003)
      Original Format: 3/4" Umatic videocassette
      Duration: 00:17:00
    - The Judson Project: Al Carmines and Deborah Hay. Interviewed by Wendy Perron and Sally Banes., 1981; ID: 094.0004 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0004, Box Shared Fales PM 13, Case 094.0033, Case 094.0004)
      Duration: 00:58:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0032)
    - The Judson Project: Lucinda Childs. Interviewed by Amanda Degener., 1981; ID: 094.0005 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0005, Box Shared Fales PM 13, Case 094.0036, Case 094.0005)
      Duration: 00:30:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0035)
    - The Judson Project: Philip Corner. Interviewed by Sally Banes., 1981; ID: 094.0006 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0006, Case 094.0006)
      Duration: 00:37:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0038)
    - The Judson Project: Simone Forti. Interviewed by Meg Cottam., 1981; ID: 094.0007 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0007, Case 094.0007)
      Duration: 00:45:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0041)
    - The Judson Project: David Gordon. Interviewed by Christine Svene., 1981; ID: 094.0008 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0008, Case 094.0008)
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0044)
    - The Judson Project: Group Shoot - Trisha Brown, Alex Hay, Robert Rauschenberg; Part I. Interviewed by Sally Banes., 1981; ID: 094.0009 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0009, Case 094.0009)
      Duration: 00:51:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0047)
    - The Judson Project: Group Shoot - Trisha Brown, Alex Hay, Robert Rauschenberg; Part II. Interviewed by Sally Banes., 1981; ID: 094.0010 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0010, Case 094.0010)
      Duration: 00:24:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0050)
    - The Judson Project: John Herbert McDowell. Interviewed by Michael Rowe., 1981; ID: 094.0011 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0011, Case 094.0011)
      Duration: 00:28:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0053)
    - The Judson Project: Jackson Maclow. Interviewed by Michael Rowe., 1981; ID: 094.0012 (Box 80, Media ID: 094.0012, Case 094.0012)
      Duration: 00:48:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0056)
    - The Judson Project: Phoebe Neville. Interviewed by Amanda Degener., 1981; ID: 094.0013 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0013, Case 094.0013)
      Duration: 00:52:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0059)
    - The Judson Project: Aileen Pasloff. Interviewed by Sally Banes., 1981; ID: 094.0014 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0014, Case 094.0014)
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0062)
    - The Judson Project: Steve Paxton. Interviewed by Nancy Stark Smith., 1981; ID: 094.0015 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0015, Case 094.0015)
      Duration: 01:01:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0065)
    - The Judson Project: Yvonne Rainer. Interviewed by Wendy Perron., 1981; ID: 094.0016 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0016, Case 094.0016)
      Duration: 00:55:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0068)
    - The Judson Project: Carolee Schneemann. Interviewed by Daniel Cameron., 1981; ID: 094.0017 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0017, Case 094.0017)
      Duration: 00:40:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0071)
    - The Judson Project: Elaine Summers. Interviewed by Tony Carruthers., 1981; ID: 094.0018 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0018, Case 094.0018)
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0074)
    - M & M Luncheon, 6/18/1991., ID: 094.0019 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0019, Case 094.0019)
      Duration: 01:05:00
    - Robert Mapplethorpe, 1988 (Arena / BBC). Directed by Nigel Finch., ID: 094.0020 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0020, Case 094.0020)
    - "Tatyana Repina"; Performance at Judson, 4/16/1978., ID: 094.0021 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0021, Case 094.0021)
      Original Format: 1/2" open reel videocassette
      Duration: 00:49:00
      DVD access copy available. (Also available on VHS. To view on VHS, please request ID #094.0077)
    - Another Pilgrim - film by Elaine Summers [c.1969]., ID: 094.0022 (Box 81, Media ID: 094.0022, Case 094.0022)
      Duration: 00:41:00
  - Subseries 4: Motion Picture Film
    - Austrian Television Report on Al Carmine's The Sayings of Mao Tse-Tung, circa 1968; ID: 094.057A (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0157A, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss094_0057A)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      16mm film, 150 ft, 4 min. 10 sec, Black and White, Sound
    - Sunday School Christmas Play Rehearsal, 1966; ID: 094.0188 (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0188, Box Digitized Access Files, File 094.0188)
      Scope and Contents
      Images of children rehearsing for the 1966 Judson Christmas Play. "M Sadan" is named on the original film reel.
      16mm film, 300 ft., 8 min. 20 sec., Black and White, Silent
    - Untitled Peter Whitehead Film, undated; ID: 094.0079 (Reel 094.0079, Media ID: 094.0079)
- Series H: Archived Websites, September 2019-ongoing; 12 websites in 12 archived websites.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Google Drive documents cannot be played back at this time.
  Accruals
  https://www.judson.org/ is accrued monthly. https://us2.campaign-archive.com/home/?u=1de038d05fb41cf0a5e52f609&id=514493bc3b is accrued quarterly. http://www.theempathyproject.org/, https://www.bringjeanhome.org/ and https://www.youtube.com/user/JudsonMemorialChurh/videos/ are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of judson.org, tumblr.com, us2.campaign-archive.com, bringjeanhome.org, theempathyproject.org, and eepurl.com in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Judson Memorial Church, located in Greenwich Village, is a place of worship that supports performing arts, social services, social justice, and participates in projects related to harm-reduction for IV drug users, reproductive justice, support for migrants, and other issues. Their website details upcoming events and ongoing service projects, solicits donations, provides information about services like a gym and childcare program, sanctuary churches, and posts video sermons and photographs of church activities. The series also includes the original defunct Judson Memorial Church website, http://classic.judson.org/, as well a number of tumblr blog projects. Judson's Front Yard is a tumblr page that documents in images, text, and video the activism occurring in Washington Square Park (i.e. the "front yard" of Judson Memorial Church). Judson Repro is a tumblr page created to document testimony by Judson Memorial Church members affirming the compatibility of Christian faith and belief in the right to reproductive autonomy. J2D 4U& mi is a tumblr page that documents (in photos) handmade signs that are posted around the Judson Memorial Church. These signs concern everything from outreach and activism at the church to youth holiday activities. Judson Windows is a tumblr page dedicated to the John La Farge designed stained glass windows within the Judson Memorial Church, with images and descriptions of each. The series also contains their newsletter, Judson's Digital Fountain.
  Bring Jean Home was an action campaign organized by the Judson Memorial Church to reverse the deportation of Jean Montrevil, an immigration rights activist and Judson member, to Haiti and allow his to return to the United States. In October 2021, Montrevil was allowed to return to the United States due to a special interest parole. As of this writing (November 2021) the website also provides information on efforts to keep him in the United States.
  The Judson Memorial Church YouTube channel features videos containing sermons; highlights from Magic Time, Bailout Theater, and the GYM performances; choir performances; social justice lectures and events; protest footage; and other music and dance performances. In 2020, Judson shifted to online Sunday services due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
  Also include the Empathy Project, a website created by Judson Memorial Church to assist Christians with reproductive decisions, specifically support of abortion. The website contains a toolkit for congregations and clergy. The toolkit includes resources to promote discussions, reading groups, worship services, and counseling in order to help a church be better prepared to support women and families in making decisions about reproductive health, abortion and sexuality.
- Ephemera
  - Buttons from Pledge Drives, Rallies, the Judson Bazaar and the Christmas Appeal, Sample Copper Shingle for the Judson Memorial Church Building, Copper Printing Plate., undated (Box 85)
- Accretion 2001- Series A: Arts
  - Subseries 1: Arts-General
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Cabarets (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Dance Events (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Events Correspondence (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Events Subcommittee (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Indices to Judson Files, Costume Inventory for Christmas Rappings (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) -Multi-Media File (photographs of Annie Sprinkle) (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Multi Media Art Show (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Oldenberg, Claes -- Bio (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Programs (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Theater Events (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) -Visual Arts Committee (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 1/4/90 -- Yoko Ono - "In Facing" (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 1/19/90 -- Yoko Ono - Cross Installation (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 1/19/90 -- Yoko Ono - Cross Installation -- Contact Sheets (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 2/90 -- Al Carmines (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 2/90 -- Al Carmines/David Vaughan -- Valentine's Day Press Release (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 2/90 -- Al Carmines/David Vaughan -- Reservation Sheets (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 2/90 -- "A Bouquet of Songs for Valentine's Day" (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 2/90 -- Al Carmines/David Vaughan - Contact Sheets (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 3/9/90 -- Campaign Kickoff Party - Photographs and Negatives (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - 3/15/90 - 3/17/90 -- La Gran Scena Opera Co. - Programs (Box 96, Folder 21)